Guide to the Duke Endowment Archives, 1902-2018 and undated, bulk 1925-2006 RL.00332
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Controller's Office Series (RESTRICTED), 1924-2008 and undated
  - Journals:
    - Journal No. 7, 1960-1965 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 46)
    - Journal No. 7, 1960-1965 (2 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 46)
    - Journal No. 7, 1960-1965 (3 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 46)
    - Journal No. 7, 1960-1965 (4 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 46)
    - Journal No. 8, 1966-1970 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box CO 46)
    - Journal No. 8, 1966-1970 (2 of 2) (Oversize-box CO 47)
    - Journal No. 9, 1971-1975 (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 47)
    - Journal No. 9, 1971-1975 (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 47)
    - Journal No. 9, 1971-1975 (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 47)
    - Journal No. 10, 1976-1980 (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 48)
    - Journal No. 10, 1976-1980 (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 48)
    - Journal No. 10, 1976-1980 (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 48)
    - No. 11, 1981-1985, bound with Cash Receipts No. 12 (Oversize-box CO 48)
    - No. 12, 1986-1997, 3 folders (Box CO 7)
  - Cashbooks (bound):
    - Cashbook No. 1, 1924-1928 (Oversize-box CO 49)
    - Cashbook: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Dec, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1930 Aug (1 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 50)
    - Cashbook: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Dec, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1930 Aug (2 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 50)
    - Cashbook: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Dec, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1930 Aug (3 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 50)
    - Cashbook: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Dec, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1930 Aug (4 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 50)
    - Cashbook: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Dec, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1930 Aug (5 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 51)
    - Cashbook: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Dec, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1930 Aug (6 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 51)
    - Cashbook: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Dec, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1930 Aug (7 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 51)
    - Cashbook: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Dec, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1930 Aug (8 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 51)
    - Cashbook No. 2, 1929-1933 Mar (Oversize-box CO 52)
    - Cashbook No. 3, 1933 Apr-1938 Jun (Oversize-box CO 53)
    - Cashbook No. 4, 1938 Jul-1944 Jun (Oversize-box CO 54)
    - Cashbook No. 5, 1945 Jul-1947 Dec (Oversize-box CO 55)
    - Cash Receipts No. 6, 1948-1955 (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 56)
    - Cash Receipts No. 6, 1948-1955 (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 56)
    - Cash Receipts No. 6, 1948-1955 (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 56)
    - Cash Receipts No. 7, 1956-1959 (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 56)
    - Cash Receipts No. 7, 1956-1959 (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 56)
    - Cash Receipts No. 7, 1956-1959 (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 57)
    - Cash Receipts No. 8, 1960-1965 (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 57)
    - Cash Receipts No. 8, 1960-1965 (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 57)
    - Cash Receipts No. 8, 1960-1965 (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 57)
    - Cash Receipts No. 9, 1966-1970 (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 57)
    - Cash Receipts No. 9, 1966-1970 (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 58)
    - Cash Receipts No. 9, 1966-1970 (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 58)
    - Cash Receipts No. 10, 1971-1975 (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 58)
    - Cash Receipts No. 10, 1971-1975 (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 58)
    - Cash Receipts No. 10, 1971-1975 (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 58)
    - Cash Receipts No. 11, 1976-1980 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 59)
    - Cash Receipts No. 11, 1976-1980 (2 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 59)
    - Cash Receipts No. 11, 1976-1980 (3 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 59)
    - Cash Receipts No. 11, 1976-1980 (4 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 59)
    - Cash Receipts No. 12 (bound with Journal No. 11), 1981-1985 (1 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 60)
    - Cash Receipts No. 12 (bound with Journal No. 11), 1981-1985 (2 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 60)
    - Cash Receipts No. 12 (bound with Journal No. 11), 1981-1985 (3 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 60)
    - Cash Receipts No. 12 (bound with Journal No. 11), 1981-1985 (4 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 60)
    - Cash Receipts No. 12 (bound with Journal No. 11), 1981-1985 (5 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 60)
    - Cash Receipts No. 12 (bound with Journal No. 11), 1981-1985 (6 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 61)
    - Cash Receipts No. 12 (bound with Journal No. 11), 1981-1985 (7 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 61)
    - Cash Receipts No. 12 (bound with Journal No. 11), 1981-1985 (8 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 61)
    - No. 13, 1986-1995, 4 folders (Box CO 8-9)
  - Subsidiary Bond Ledgers:
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 1, 1927-1943 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box CO 61)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 1, 1927-1943 (2 of 2) (Oversize-box CO 61)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 2, 1927-1945 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box CO 62)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 2, 1927-1945 (2 of 2) (Oversize-box CO 62)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 3A, 1936-1959 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 62)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 3A, 1936-1959 (2 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 62)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 3A, 1936-1959 (3 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 63)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 3A, 1936-1959 (4 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 63)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 3B, 1936-1959 (1 of 5) (Oversize-box CO 63)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 3B, 1936-1959 (2 of 5) (Oversize-box CO 63)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 3B, 1936-1959 (3 of 5) (Oversize-box CO 63)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 3B, 1936-1959 (4 of 5) (Oversize-box CO 64)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 3B, 1936-1959 (5 of 5) (Oversize-box CO 64)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 3C, 1936-1959 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 64)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 3C, 1936-1959 (2 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 64)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 3C, 1936-1959 (3 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 64)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 3C, 1936-1959 (4 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 65)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 4A, 1960-1965 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 65)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 4A, 1960-1965 (2 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 65)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 4A, 1960-1965 (3 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 65)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 4A, 1960-1965 (4 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 65)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 4B, 1960-1965 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 66)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 4B, 1960-1965 (2 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 66)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 4B, 1960-1965 (3 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 66)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 4B, 1960-1965 (4 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 66)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 5, 1966-1970 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 66)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 5, 1966-1970 (2 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 67)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 5, 1966-1970 (3 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 67)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 5, 1966-1970 (4 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 67)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 6, 1971-1975 (1 of 5) (Oversize-box CO 67)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 6, 1971-1975 (2 of 5) (Oversize-box CO 68)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 6, 1971-1975 (3 of 5) (Oversize-box CO 68)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 6, 1971-1975 (4 of 5) (Oversize-box CO 68)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 6, 1971-1975 (5 of 5) (Oversize-box CO 68)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 7, 1976-1980 (1 of 6) (Oversize-box CO 68)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 7, 1976-1980 (2 of 6) (Oversize-box CO 69)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 7, 1976-1980 (3 of 6) (Oversize-box CO 69)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 7, 1976-1980 (4 of 6) (Oversize-box CO 69)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 7, 1976-1980 (5 of 6) (Oversize-box CO 69)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 7, 1976-1980 (6 of 6) (Oversize-box CO 69)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 8, 1981-1985 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 70)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 8, 1981-1985 (2 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 70)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 8, 1981-1985 (3 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 70)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 8, 1981-1985 (4 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 70)
    - No. 9, 1986-1995, 9 folders (Box CO 10-11)
  - Vault and Dividend Records:
    - Vault & Dividend Record No. 1A, 1943-1959, Stocks (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 71)
    - Vault & Dividend Record No. 1A, 1943-1959, Stocks (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 71)
    - Vault & Dividend Record No. 1A, 1943-1959, Stocks (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 71)
    - Vault & Dividend Record No. 1B, 1943-1959, Bonds, Notes (US) (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 71)
    - Vault & Dividend Record No. 1B, 1943-1959, Bonds, Notes (US) (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 71)
    - Vault & Dividend Record No. 1B, 1943-1959, Bonds, Notes (US) (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 72)
    - Vault & Dividend Record No. 2, DU Accounts 1960-1962, DE Accounts 1960-1965 (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 72)
    - Vault & Dividend Record No. 2, DU Accounts 1960-1962, DE Accounts 1960-1965 (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 72)
    - Vault & Dividend Record No. 2, DU Accounts 1960-1962, DE Accounts 1960-1965 (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 72)
    - Vault & Dividend Record No. 3, 1966-1970 (Oversize-box CO 73)
    - Vault & Divident Record No. 4, 1971-1975 (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 73)
    - Vault & Divident Record No. 4, 1971-1975 (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 73)
    - Vault & Divident Record No. 4, 1971-1975 (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 73)
    - Vault & Divident Record No. 5, 1976-1980 (1 of 5) (Oversize-box CO 74)
    - Vault & Divident Record No. 5, 1976-1980 (2 of 5) (Oversize-box CO 74)
    - Vault & Divident Record No. 5, 1976-1980 (3 of 5) (Oversize-box CO 74)
    - Vault & Divident Record No. 5, 1976-1980 (4 of 5) (Oversize-box CO 74)
    - Vault & Divident Record No. 5, 1976-1980 (5 of 5) (Oversize-box CO 75)
    - Vault & Dividend Record No. 6, 1981-1985 (1 of 7) (Oversize-box CO 75)
    - Vault & Dividend Record No. 6, 1981-1985 (2 of 7) (Oversize-box CO 75)
    - Vault & Dividend Record No. 6, 1981-1985 (3 of 7) (Oversize-box CO 75)
    - Vault & Dividend Record No. 6, 1981-1985 (4 of 7) (Oversize-box CO 76)
    - Vault & Dividend Record No. 6, 1981-1985 (5 of 7) (Oversize-box CO 76)
    - Vault & Dividend Record No. 6, 1981-1985 (6 of 7) (Oversize-box CO 76)
    - Vault & Dividend Record No. 6, 1981-1985 (7 of 7) (Oversize-box CO 76)
    - No. 7, 1985-1993, 5 folders (Box CO 12)
      Donor's note: as of the end of 1993, bond transactions will no longer be posted to the Vault Ledger. Bond activity will be reported in the GIA Ledger and in the Subsidiary Ledger.
    - No. 8, 1985-1993, 5 folders (Box CO 13)
  - Agency Account Books:
    - Ledgers:
      - Ledger Volume No. 1, 1963-1967 (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 77)
      - Ledger Volume No. 1, 1963-1967 (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 77)
      - Ledger Volume No. 1, 1963-1967 (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 77)
      - Ledger Volume No. 2, 1968-1972 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 77)
      - Ledger Volume No. 2, 1968-1972 (2 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 78)
      - Ledger Volume No. 2, 1968-1972 (3 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 78)
      - Ledger Volume No. 2, 1968-1972 (4 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 78)
    - Cashbooks and Journals:
      - Cashbooks and Journal Volume No. 1, 1963-1967 (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 78)
      - Cashbooks and Journal Volume No. 1, 1963-1967 (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 78)
      - Cashbooks and Journal Volume No. 1, 1963-1967 (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 79)
      - Cashbooks and Journal No. 2, 1968-1972 (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 79)
      - Cashbooks and Journal No. 2, 1968-1972 (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 79)
      - Cashbooks and Journal No. 2, 1968-1972 (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 79)
      - Cashbooks and Journal No. 3, 1968-1972 Jun (includes AA Ledger No. 3, 1972 Jul-1974 Apr) (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 80)
      - Cashbooks and Journal No. 3, 1968-1972 Jun (includes AA Ledger No. 3, 1972 Jul-1974 Apr) (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 80)
      - Cashbooks and Journal No. 3, 1968-1972 Jun (includes AA Ledger No. 3, 1972 Jul-1974 Apr) (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 80)
    - Subsidiary Bond Ledgers:
      - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 1, 1963-1967 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 81)
      - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 1, 1963-1967 (2 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 81)
      - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 1, 1963-1967 (3 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 81)
      - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 1, 1963-1967 (4 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 81)
      - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 2., 1968-1972 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 82)
      - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 2., 1968-1972 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 82)
      - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 2., 1968-1972 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 82)
      - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 2., 1968-1972 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 82)
    - Vault Registers:
      - Vault Register No. 1, 1963-1967 (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 83)
      - Vault Register No. 1, 1963-1967 (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 83)
      - Vault Register No. 1, 1963-1967 (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 83)
      - Vault Register No. 2, 1968-1972 Jun (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 84)
      - Vault Register No. 2, 1968-1972 Jun (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 84)
      - Vault Register No. 2, 1968-1972 Jun (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 84)
      - Subsidiary and Vault Register No. 3, 1972 Jul-1974 Apr (1 of 2) (Oversize-box CO 85)
      - Subsidiary and Vault Register No. 3, 1972 Jul-1974 Apr (2 of 2) (Oversize-box CO 85)
  - Payroll Records:
    - Record Book, 1925-1942 (includes Estate of James B. Duke, Trust Under Will, Duke University construction, Doris Duke Trust, and Angier B. Duke Memorial, Inc.) (Oversize-box CO 85)
    - Control Journal, 1966 Oct.-1967, (includes Payroll Register, Miscellaneous Deduction Journal) (Oversize-box CO 85)
    - Control Journal, 1968 (Oversize-box CO 85)
    - Control Journal, 1969 (Oversize-box CO 85)
    - Register, 1970 (Oversize-box CO 85)
    - Register, 1971 (Oversize-box CO 85)
    - Change Journal, 1966 Oct.-1967 (Oversize-box CO 85)
    - Change Journal, 1968 (Oversize-box CO 85)
    - Change Journal, 1969 (Oversize-box CO 85)
    - Transaction Proof Report, 1970 (Oversize-box CO 85)
    - Transaction Proof Report, 1971 (Oversize-box CO 85)
  - Voucher Records:
    - Voucher Record No. 1, 1924 Dec-1929 Dec (Oversize-box CO 86)
    - Voucher Record No. 2, 1929 Jun-1933 Apr (Oversize-box CO 86)
    - Voucher Record: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Nov, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1933 (1 of 11) (Oversize-box CO 88)
    - Voucher Record: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Nov, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1933 (2 of 11) (Oversize-box CO 88)
    - Voucher Record: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Nov, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1933 (3 of 11) (Oversize-box CO 88)
    - Voucher Record: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Nov, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1933 (4 of 11) (Oversize-box CO 88)
    - Voucher Record: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Nov, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1933 (5 of 11) (Oversize-box CO 89)
    - Voucher Record: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Nov, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1933 (6 of 11) (Oversize-box CO 89)
    - Voucher Record: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Nov, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1933 (7 of 11) (Oversize-box CO 89)
    - Voucher Record: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Nov, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1933 (8 of 11) (Oversize-box CO 89)
    - Voucher Record: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Nov, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1933 (9 of 11) (Oversize-box CO 90)
    - Voucher Record: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Nov, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1933 (10 of 11) (Oversize-box CO 90)
    - Voucher Record: The Duke Endowment, 1927 Mar-Nov, Duke Construction Co., 1927 Dec-1933 (11 of 11) (Oversize-box CO 90)
    - Voucher Record No. 3, 1933 May-1937 Apr (Oversize-box CO 91)
    - Voucher Record No. 4, 1937 May-1940 Dec (Oversize-box CO 91)
    - Voucher Record No. 5, 1941-1947 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 92)
    - Voucher Record No. 5, 1941-1947 (2 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 92)
    - Voucher Record No. 5, 1941-1947 (3 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 92)
    - Voucher Record No. 5, 1941-1947 (4 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 92)
  - Disbursement Registers:
    - Disbursement Register No. 6, 1948-1952 (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 93)
    - Disbursement Register No. 6, 1948-1952 (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 93)
    - Disbursement Register No. 6, 1948-1952 (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 93)
    - Disbursement Register No. 7, 1953-1956 (1 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 93)
    - Disbursement Register No. 7, 1953-1956 (2 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 93)
    - Disbursement Register No. 7, 1953-1956 (3 of 3) (Oversize-box CO 93)
    - Disbursement Register No. 8, 1957-1959 (1 of 2) (Oversize-box CO 94)
    - Disbursement Register No. 8, 1957-1959 (2 of 2) (Oversize-box CO 94)
    - Disbursement Register No. 9, 1960-1962 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 94)
    - Disbursement Register No. 9, 1960-1962 (2 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 94)
    - Disbursement Register No. 9, 1960-1962 (3 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 94)
    - Disbursement Register No. 9, 1960-1962 (4 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 95)
    - Disbursement Register No. 10, 1963-1965 (1 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 95)
    - Disbursement Register No. 10, 1963-1965 (2 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 95)
    - Disbursement Register No. 10, 1963-1965 (3 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 95)
    - Disbursement Register No. 10, 1963-1965 (4 of 4) (Oversize-box CO 95)
    - Disbursement Register No. 11, 1966-1970 (1 of 6) (Oversize-box CO 96)
    - Disbursement Register No. 11, 1966-1970 (2 of 6) (Oversize-box CO 96)
    - Disbursement Register No. 11, 1966-1970 (3 of 6) (Oversize-box CO 96)
    - Disbursement Register No. 11, 1966-1970 (4 of 6) (Oversize-box CO 96)
    - Disbursement Register No. 11, 1966-1970 (5 of 6) (Oversize-box CO 96)
    - Disbursement Register No. 11, 1966-1970 (6 of 6) (Oversize-box CO 97)
    - Disbursement Register No. 12, 1971-1975 (1 of 7) (Oversize-box CO 97)
    - Disbursement Register No. 12, 1971-1975 (2 of 7) (Oversize-box CO 97)
    - Disbursement Register No. 12, 1971-1975 (3 of 7) (Oversize-box CO 97)
    - Disbursement Register No. 12, 1971-1975 (4 of 7) (Oversize-box CO 97)
    - Disbursement Register No. 12, 1971-1975 (5 of 7) (Oversize-box CO 98)
    - Disbursement Register No. 12, 1971-1975 (6 of 7) (Oversize-box CO 98)
    - Disbursement Register No. 12, 1971-1975 (7 of 7) (Oversize-box CO 98)
    - Disbursement Register No. 13, 1976-1980 (1 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 98)
    - Disbursement Register No. 13, 1976-1980 (2 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 99)
    - Disbursement Register No. 13, 1976-1980 (3 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 99)
    - Disbursement Register No. 13, 1976-1980 (4 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 99)
    - Disbursement Register No. 13, 1976-1980 (5 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 99)
    - Disbursement Register No. 13, 1976-1980 (6 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 100)
    - Disbursement Register No. 13, 1976-1980 (7 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 100)
    - Disbursement Register No. 13, 1976-1980 (8 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 100)
    - Disbursement Register No. 14, 1981-1985 (1 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 100)
    - Disbursement Register No. 14, 1981-1985 (2 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 101)
    - Disbursement Register No. 14, 1981-1985 (3 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 101)
    - Disbursement Register No. 14, 1981-1985 (4 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 101)
    - Disbursement Register No. 14, 1981-1985 (5 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 101)
    - Disbursement Register No. 14, 1981-1985 (6 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 102)
    - Disbursement Register No. 14, 1981-1985 (7 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 102)
    - Disbursement Register No. 14, 1981-1985 (8 of 8) (Oversize-box CO 102)
    - No. 15, Expense, 1986-1990, Folders 1-4 of 6 (Box CO 14)
    - No. 15, Expense, 1986-1990, Folders 5-6 of 6 (Box CO 15)
    - No. 16, Expense, 1991-1985, Folders 1-2 of 6 (Box CO 15)
    - No. 16, Expense, 1991-1985, Folders 3-6 of 6 (Box CO 16)
    - No. 17, Securities, 1986-1995, 3 folders (Box CO 17)
  - Credit card receipts: (Box CO 18)
    - 1995, 5 folders (Box CO 18)
    - 1996, Folders 1-2 of 6 (Box CO 18)
    - 1996, Folders 3-6 of 6 (Box CO 19)
  - Microfilm Reels, 1924-1947, 1978:
    - No. 1, Negative (Box CO 20)
      - Ledger No. 1, 1924-1928 (Box CO 20)
      - Ledger No. 2, 1929-1936 (Box CO 20)
    - No. 2, Negative
      - Journal No. 1, 1924-1929 Jan. (Box CO 20)
      - Journal No. 2, 1929 Feb.-1936 May (Box CO 20)
      - Cashbook No. 1, 1924-1928 (Box CO 20)
    - No. 3, Negative
      - Cashbook No. 2, 1929-1933 Mar. (Box CO 20)
      - Subsidiary Bond Ledger No. 1, 1927-1943 (Box CO 20)
    - No. 4, Negative
      - Voucher Record No. 1, 1924 Dec.-1929 May (Box CO 20)
      - Voucher Record No. 2, 1929 June-1933 Apr. (Box CO 20)
      - Cashbook, 1927 Mar.-Nov. (Box CO 20)
      - Secretary's Reports, 1941-1946 (Box CO 20)
    - No. 5, Negative
      - Secretary's Reports, 1925-1940 (Box CO 20)
      - Inventory of The Duke Endowment Archives, 1978 (Box CO 20)
    - No. 6, Positive
      - Cashbook No. 3, 1933 Apr.-1938 June (Box CO 20)
      - Cashbook No. 4, 1938 July-1944 June (Box CO 20)
      - Journal No. 3, 1936 June-1945 May (Box CO 20)
    - No. 6A, Negative
      - Cashbook No. 3, 1933 Apr.-1938 June (Box CO 20)
      - Cashbook No. 4, 1938 July-1944 June (Box CO 20)
      - Journal No. 3, 1936 June-1945 May (Box CO 20)
    - No. 7, Positive
      - Journal No. 3, 1936 June-1945 May (Box CO 20)
      - Ledger No. 3, 1937-1945 (Box CO 20)
      - Voucher Record No. 3, 1933 May-1937 Apr. (Box CO 20)
      - Voucher Record No. 4, 1937 May-1940 Dec. (Box CO 20)
    - No. 7A, Negative
      - Journal No. 3, 1936 June-1945 May (Box CO 20)
      - Ledger No. 3, 1937-1945 (Box CO 20)
      - Voucher Record No. 3, 1933 May-1937 Apr. (Box CO 20)
      - Voucher Record No. 4, 1937 May-1940 Dec. (Box CO 20)
    - No. 8, Positive
      - Voucher Record No. 5, 1941-1947 (Box CO 20)
      - Bond Ledger No. 2, 1927-1945 (Box CO 20)
      - Books of Account Subseries (Box CO 20)
    - No. 8A, Negative
      - Voucher Record No. 5, 1941-1947 (Box CO 20)
      - Bond Ledger No. 2, 1927-1945 (Box CO 20)
    - No. 9, Positive
      - Duke Construction Company, 1927-1933
        - General Ledger, 1927 Mar.-Nov. (Box CO 20)
        - Journal, 1927 Mar.-Dec. (Box CO 20)
        - Voucher Records, 1927 Mar.-Nov. (Box CO 20)
    - No. 9A, Positive
      - Duke Construction Company (continued) (Box CO 20)
    - No. 10, Negative
      - Duke Construction Company, 1927-1933
        - General Ledger, 1927 Mar.-Nov. (Box CO 20)
        - Journal, 1927 Mar.-Dec. (Box CO 20)
        - Voucher Records, 1927 Mar.-Nov. (Box CO 20)
    - No. 10A, Negative
      - Duke Construction Company (continued) (Box CO 20)
  - Microfilm Reels, 1996-2003:, Rolls 1-6 and 8-10 of 10, all negative
    - No. 1 (Box CO 20)
      - Start: Appropriation Ledger, 1998 Dec.; End: Disbursements/Receipts/Expenses/Beneficiaries, 1998 Jan. (Box CO 20)
    - No. 2
      - Start: Securities Cash Receipts/Cash Disbursements Ledger, 1997; End: Cash Receipts/Cash Disbursements Ledger, 1999 July (Box CO 20)
    - No. 3
      - Start: Securities Cash Receipts Disbursements, 1996 Dec.; End: Disbursements/Receipts/Expenses/Beneficiaries, 1997 Jan. (Box CO 20)
    - No. 4
      - Start: Appropriation Ledger, 2000 Dec.; End: Cash Receipts/Cash Disbursements Ledger, 2000 Jan. (Box CO 20)
    - No. 5
      - Start: Securities Cash Receipts/Cash Disbursements Ledger, 1998 Dec. End: Payables Transactions, 2000 Dec. (Box CO 20)
    - No. 8
      - Start: General Ledger, 2001 Jan.; End: General Ledger, 2001 Oct. (Box CO 20)
    - No. 9
      - Start: General Ledger, 2001 Nov.; End: Committee on Finance Meetings Minutes, 1998 Sept.-2003 Oct. (Box CO 20)
    - No. 10
      - Start: Trial Balance Summary, 2000; End: Payables Transactions, 2001 Dec. (Box CO 20)
  - Microfiche, 2002:
    - General Ledger, 2002 Jan.-Dec.; Payables, 2002 (Box CO 20)
  - Compact disks, 2005-2008 and undated:
    - General Ledger and Payables transactions, 2005-2007 (Box CO 20)
    - BICOM, undated (disk created 2008 Aug.) (Box CO 20)
  - Miscellaneous Subseries, 1928-2006
    - Audit Committee:
      - Audit reports, 1928-1936, 1949-1976, 28 folders (Box CO 21)
      - Audit reports, 1977-1990, 14 folders (Box CO 22)
      - Audit reports, 1991-2001, 10 volumes (Box CO 22)
      - Audit reports, 2002-2007, 6 volumes (Box CO 23)